Guide to the Rice University Smalley Institute for Nanoscale Science and Technology records, 1993-2015 UA 184
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Smalley Institute for Nanoscale Science and Technology records
1993-2015
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Smalley, Richard E.
UA 184
14.5 Linear Feet (14 boxes)
This collection contains videos by or about the Smalley Institute and about Richard Smalley, co-winner of the Nobel Prize in chemistry. Videotapes are in VHS and Beta format. The collection also includes papers of Wade Adams during his tenure as Director of the Smalley Institute; information on nanotechnology initiatives and proposals of the Smalley Institute and others; records of staff participation in nanotechnology conferences; and administrative records of the institute. The Richard E. Smalley Institute for Nanoscale Science and Technology was founded in 1993 at Rice University and was originally named the Center for Nanoscale Science and Technology.
Biographical / Historical
The Richard E. Smalley Institute for Nanoscale Science and Technology was originally named the Center for Nanoscale Science and Technology. In 1993, Professor Richard E. Smalley envisioned the first nanotechnology center in the world. Thus, the Center for Nanoscale Science and Technology (CNST) was born. With full support from the university, CNST was tasked with defining and implementing the nanotechnology initiative at Rice University. CNST set forth a bold objective to provide a venue where researchers from all disciplines of science and engineering can come together to share ideas and discuss their views and prospects of nanoscience, nanoengineering, and nanotechnology. CNST concluded the best way to achieve this objective was to provide the administrative and technical infrastructure to conduct cutting-edge nanotechnology research, sponsor seminars and conferences, advocate entrepreneurism, encourage multi-disciplinary collaborations, connect to external organizations, and support educational initiatives from the kindergarten to the professional level.
Within 8 years, CNST had fostered the formation of a nanotechnology spin-off company (Carbon Nanotechnologies, Inc), received NSF funding for a new nanotechnology center (Center for Biological and Environmental Nanotechnology), and developed a centralized, well-managed equipment collection valued at greater than $10 million (Shared Equipment Authority). Building on this success, CNST began branching out to incorporate technical training, industry partnership, and community outreach. In 2002, CNST held the 1st Annual TunaFest Celebration, an informal venue for industry, academia, and nanotech enthusiasts to network. In just 6 years, TunaFest has grown to over 1000 attendees making it the premier nanotechnology social event of Houston. From 2002 to 2004, CNST advanced nanotechnology education through a variety of initiatives. The NanoKids program, based in Professor Tour's group, brings key concepts of nanoscience to middle school students. Additionally, CNST worked with several departments at Rice University to create undergraduate curriculum, a professional masters program, and continuing education courses in a variety of nanoscience and engineering topics.
While expanding their initiative portfolio, CNST continued cultivating its scientific strengths, fostering 10 spin-off companies, developing 5 unique nanotechnology centers and components, and growing the shared equipment at Rice University to over $12 million. By 2005, CNST supported the research efforts of 100 faculty members with over 400 graduate students spanning 14 departments at Rice University.
In 2005 after the passing of Professor Smalley, the Rice University Board of Trustees renamed the Institute in his honor.
As of 2010, the Smalley Institute included 151 faculty members in 21 departments with over 500 students researching nanotechnology in a variety of societal and scientific arenas including energy, education, aerospace, ethics, and human health; consisted of 5 major centers and components including $15 million in shared equipment and facilities for nanotechnology research; was affiliateds with 8 nanotechnology organizations in Houston and around Texas; and collaborated with over 50 associations to promote nanotechnology in all aspects of science and society.
In 2015 the Richard E. Smalley Institute for Nanoscale Science and Technology and the Rice Quantum Institute merged to form the Smalley-Curl Institute (SCI).
(Excerpted from the CNST website, http://cnst.rice.edu/history/, accessed Jan. 3, 2011.)
Richard E. Smalley was affiliated with Rice University from 1976 until his death in 2005, serving as the Gene and Norman Hackerman Professor of Chemistry at Rice beginning in 1982 and Professor of Physics at Rice beginning in 1990. A co-founder of the Rice Quantum Institute in 1979, he served as its chairman beginning in 1986, and was the director of the Center for Nanoscale Science and Technology. He was a member of the National Academy of Sciences (elected 1990), the American Academy of Arts and Sciences (elected 1991), and was the recipient of the 1991 Irving Langmuir Prize in chemical physics, the 1992 International Prize for New Materials (shared with R.F. Curl and H.W. Kroto), the 1992 E.O. Lawrence Award of the U.S. Department of Energy, the 1992 Robert A. Welch Award in Chemistry, the 1993 William H. Nichols Medal, and the 1996 Nobel Prize in Chemistry (shared with R.F. Curl and H.W. Kroto).
Smalley pioneered advances in the development of supersonic beam laser spectroscopy, super-cold pulsed beams, and laser-driven sources of free radicals, triplets, and metal and semiconductor cluster beams. He discovered and characterized fullerenes, the third elemental form of carbon after graphite and diamond, for which he was awarded the Nobel Prize.
Born June 6, 1943, in Akron, Ohio, Smalley received his bachelor's degree in chemistry in 1965 from the University of Michigan, and master's and doctorate degrees from Princeton University in 1971 and 1973.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains videos by or about the Smalley Institute and about Richard Smalley, co-winner of the Nobel Prize in Chemistry. Videotapes are in VHS and Beta format. The collection also includes papers of Wade Adams during his tenure as Director of the Smalley Institute; information on nanotechnology initiatives and proposals of the Smalley Institute and others; records of staff participation in nanotechnology conferences; and administrative records of the institute. These materials include correspondence, various publications, and some financial records.
Access Restrictions
This material is open for research.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Tranferred by the Smalley Institute at Rice University, delivered by Douglas Killgore, March 25, 2008. Additions to the collection were transferred by the Smalley Institute in 2013, 2014, 2015, and 2016.
Related Materials
Materials related to the Smalley Institute for Nanoscale Science and Technology records can be found in the Richard Smalley Papers (UA 184, 1943-2007, Woodson Research Center, Fondren Library, Rice University).
Index Terms
Subjects
Nanotechnology; Universities and colleges
Document Types
videotapes; interviews
Subjects (Corporations)
Rice University. Richard E. Smalley Institute for Nanoscale Science and Technology
- Series I: Audio & video tapes, 1993-2007; 166954
  - Chemistry Nobel Award (VHS), 108033 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Chemistry Nobel Award (VHS), 108034 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Chemistry Nobel Award (VHS), 108035 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Chemistry Nobel Award (VHS), 108036 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "Smalley & Curl Awarded Nobel Prize" October 14-19, 1996: Houston Coverage (VHS), 108037 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "Curl & Smalley Awarded Nobel Prize" October 11-13, 1996: Houston Coverage (VHS), 108038 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - "Smalley & Curl Awarded Nobel Prize" October 14-19, 1996: Houston Coverage (VHS), 108039 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - "Curl & Smalley Awarded Nobel Prize" October 09-10, 1996: Houston and Cable Coverage (VHS), 108040 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - "Curl & Smalley Awarded Nobel Prize" October 09-10, 1996: Houston and Cable Coverage (VHS), 108041 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - "Nobel Prize Winners": Houston Informed KTFH-TV (Ind) Houston; December 19, 1996 7:30-8:00 AM (VHS), 108042 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - "Curl & Smalley/Nobel Prize" October 09, 1996: Houston, Cable, & Network Coverage (VHS), 108043 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - "Chemistry Award" CNN-TV Cable; December 08, 1996 12:00-1:00 PM (VHS), 108044 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - "Chemistry Award" Nobel 1996: CNN-TV Cable; December 08, 1996 12:00-1:00 PM (VHS), 108045 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - "Chemistry Award" Nobel 1996: CNN-TV Cable; December 08, 1996 12:00-1:00 PM (VHS), 108046 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - "Chemistry Award" Nobel 1996: CNN-TV Cable; December 08, 1996 12:00-1:00 PM (VHS), 108047 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - "Chemistry Award" Nobel 1996: CNN-TV Cable; December 08, 1996 12:00-1:00 PM (VHS), 108048 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - "Chemistry Award" Nobel 1996: CNN-TV Cable; December 08, 1996 12:00-1:00 PM (VHS), 108049 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - CNN Nobel Minds 1996 (VHS), 108050 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Nobel 1996 (VHS), 108051 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Nobel 1996 (VHS), 108052 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "Nobel Minds: Challenges of the 21st Century" CNN-TV Cable; December 15, 1996 1:00-2:00 PM (VHS), 108053 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Texas Video & Post Nanotopia (VHS), 108054 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - National Science Foundation: Nanotechnology Symposium 3/19/02; Lecture: Dr. Richard Smalley (VHS), 108055 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Richard E. Smalley 10-8-92 (Beta), 108056 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Nano-Groundbreaking 4-30-96 (Beta), 108057 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Nano-Groundbreaking 4-30-96 (Beta), 108058 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Nano-Groundbreaking 4-30-96 (Beta), 108059 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Groundbreaking Original: SWMT Ribbon cutting for groundbreaking ceremony (VHS), 108060 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Ropes - Ground Breaking Tape 1: Computer Graphics & TEM views (VHS), 108061 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Groundbreaking Tape 2: Ribbon Cutting – microscopic view (VHS), 108062 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Ropes - Ground Breaking Tape 1: Computer Graphics & TEM views (VHS), 108063 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Groundbreaking Tape 2: Ribbon Cutting – microscopic view (VHS), 108064 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Los Alamos National Lab Director's Colloquium: Buckey Balls and Nanotubes: Dr. Rick Smalley 12/13/00 (VHS), 108065 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - ONR Nanotube Conference 05.30.97-06.01.97; 3 of 3 (VHS), 108066 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - ONR Nanotube Conference 05.30.97-06.01.97; 3 of 3 (VHS), 108067 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - ONR Nanotube Conference 05.30.97-06.01.97; 2 of 3 (VHS), 108068 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - ONR Nanotube Conference 05.30.97-06.01.97; 2 of 3 (VHS), 108069 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - ONR Nanotube Conference 05.30.97-06.01.97; 1 of 3 (VHS), 108070 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - ONR Nanotube Conference 05.30.97-06.01.97; 1 of 3 (VHS), 108071 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - ONR Nanotube Conf. 5/30-6/1, 1997; 1 of 3 (VHS), 108072 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - ONR Nanotechnology Conference 5/30/97-6/1/97; 2 of 3 (VHS), 108073 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - ONR Nanotechnology Conf. 5/30/97-6/1/97; 3 of 3 (VHS), 108074 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Tehcnion – Israel Institute of Technology: Honorary Doctorate Conferment Ceremnony 2004: Prof. Richard E. Smalley; June 14, 2004 (VHS), 108075 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - MMETS 2000: Dr. Richard Smalley: Engineer's Club (VHS), 108076 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Smalley @ UOP 6-3-97 (VHS), 108077 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Fourth John C. Polanyi Nobel Laureate Lecture Series: November 28, 2000 (VHS), 108078 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Fourth John C. Polanyi Nobel Laureate Lecture Series: November 28, 2000 (VHS), 108079 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Smalley AF Intro 10/17/02 (VHS), 108080 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Nanospace (VHS), 108081 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - "Race to Catch a Buckyball" Nova PBS-TV Network; December 19, 1995 8:00-9:00 PM (VHS), 108082 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Animation of bucky cable lifting destroyer (copy) (VHS), 108083 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Buckey Cable Animation (Version 2) 06/11/97 (VHS), 108084 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - ONR (VHS), 108085 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - TEM Environmental Cell Studies of Nanotubes (VHS), 108086 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - TEM Environmental Cell Studies of Nanotubes (Bromine Treated) (VHS), 108087 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Navy Ship & Cable & Nanotube animation (VHS), 108088 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - "Fun with Metals" Dr. Robert B. Pond, Sr.: American Society for Metals (Buffalo Chapter) (VHS), 108089 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Material Science Seminar: "40 Years of Fun in Metallurgy" Robert B. Pond, Sr. (VHS), 108090 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Wade Adams – Fox 26; 5-23-02 A.M. Newscast (VHS), 108091 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Note written by Richard to Doug; RE: Wade Adams & Richard Smalley's first meeting, 108092 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Wade Adams 11/12/02 (VHS), 108093 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Channel 26 11-15-05: Wade Adams Nano/Energy Conference (VHS), 108094 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - "Richard Smalley – Rice University": Amazing Science; TLC-TV Cable October 6, 1998 9:00 PM (VHS), 108095 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - "Richard Smalley – Rice University": Amazing Science; TLC-TV Cable October 6, 1998 9:00 PM (VHS), 108096 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Richard Smalley "Rehearsal Presentation" 05/02/95 (VHS), 108097 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Welch Award October 1992 (VHS), 108098 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - R.E. Smalley: Center of Nano & Tech; Promo Tape 5/2/95 version (VHS), 108099 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Buckey Ball (VHS), 108100 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Smalley in Duncan Hall "Nanotubes & Fibers" Lectures (VHS), 108101 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Nanotube fluorescence 8/2/02; Fox 26 – News at Nine (VHS), 108102 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Texas Video & Post TVP Demo 2002; 2/25/2003 (VHS), 108103 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - NANO Birthdays Celebration 11/13/03 (VHS), 108104 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Center for Nanoscale Science and Technology Rice University (VHS), 108105 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Ch. 11 News – Jan 20, 2003: Halas, Lane, Wiesner, Kulinowski (VHS), 108106 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Rotating Nanotube (black background) (VHS), 108107 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - C60 inside nanotube (VHS), 108108 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - National Science Foundation: "America's Investment in the Future" March, 2001 (VHS), 108109 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - With PRL 76 (1996) (VHS), 108110 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Powderhouse Productions: Engineering the Impossible; 1 Hour Version 4/26/02 (VHS), 108111 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - BBC Horizons: Molecule with Sunglasses & Welch Prize Piece (VHS), 108112 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - September 13, 2002 Tape 1: McMurtry Aud, Rice Univ: Governor's Council for Science and Technology (VHS), 108113 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Ch. 11 – 6 PM News 03/31/03: Wade Adams – nanotech & the military (VHS), 108114 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Biosym Technologies, Inc. Insight II (beta), 108115 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - R.E. Smalley: Nano Center Promo Tape; 5/2/95 version (VHS), 108116 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - ONR Day 1 Tripod (VHS), 108117 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - NNI Kennedy & Belk 5/23/02 (VHS), 108118 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - NNI Stringer 5/23/02 Tape 4 (VHS), 108119 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - NNI Christian Son 5/23/02 (VHS), 108120 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - NNI Gillis 5/23/02 (VHS), 108121 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - NNI Bass 5/23/02 (VHS), 108122 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - NNI Gower 5/23/02 (VHS), 108123 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - NNI Naghavi 5/23/02 (VHS), 108124 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - NNI Michalske 5/23/02 (VHS), 108125 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - NNI Carim 5/23/02 Tape 2 (VHS), 108126 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - NNI Rosenblum 5/23/02 (VHS), 108127 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - NNI Ulrich 5/23/02 (VHS), 108128 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - NNI Leff 5/23/02 (VHS), 108129 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - NNI Norman 5/23/02 (VHS), 108130 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - NNI Hosslacher/Tour 5/23/02 (VHS), 108131 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - NNI Goronkin 5/23/02 (VHS), 108132 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - NNI Mike Roco 5/23/02 (VHS), 166957 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - NNI Hosslacher 5/23/02 (VHS), 108134 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - NNI Wilson 5/23/02 (VHS), 108135 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - NNI Cox 5/23/02 (VHS), 108136 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - NNI Gibbs 5/23/02 (VHS), 108137 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - NNI Monachino 5/23/02 (VHS), 108138 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Können Tauben "Zählen" NTSC (VHS), 108139 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Noorderlicht: De vinger van God (VHS), 108140 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Webcast Teleconference: 4-way w/Smalley (VHS), 108141 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - September 13, 2002 tape 2: McMurtry Auditorium, Rice University: Governor's Council for Science and Technology (VHS), 108142 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Edwin L. Thomas; 11/22/02 (VHS), 108143 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Dept. of Physics, Univ. of Nottingham (VHS), 108144 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Physics 431/2; 10/2/96 (VHS), 108145 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - No label (cassette), 108146 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Life Sciences: Dr. James Murday (cassette), 108147 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Molecular Electronics: Dr. Harold Hosack (cassette), 108148 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Energy/Petrochemicals: Dr. Paul Barbara (cassette), 108149 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Smalley Interview/PBS: Richard Smalley (VHS), 108150 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Series II: Wade Adams (Director of the Institute, 2002-2011), 181651
  - Center for Nanoscale Science & Technology, 181904 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Institute information, 181905 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Staff meetings, 181915 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Faculty, 181916 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Walter Kohn lecture, 2006; 181906 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Richard Feynman lecture, 1959; 181910 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - International university, 181911 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - National Cheng Kung University, 181912 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Scarborough Water Project, 181913 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Stem cells programs, 181914 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - American Chemical Society Smalley Symposium, 2006; 181917 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Smalley celebration, 181918 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Clarkson Aerospace Program, 181919 (Box 4, Folder 13-14)
  - Collaborative efforts, 181920 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Nanotechnology & Cancer workshop, 2007; 181921 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Nanotechnology forums/conferences, 181922 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Nano art, 181923 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Alliance for NanoHealth, 181924 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - NanoInteract, 181925 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Nanotechnology Foundation of Texas, 181927 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Nanotechnology: Social & ethics, 181928 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Nanotechnology survey, 181929 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - nanoTX, 2007; 181908 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - NanoVance, Inc., 181930 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Site visits, 181931 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Photos/images, 181932 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Presentations, 2006-2011 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Year of the Nano, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, 2002-2011; 207472 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Brochures, 2009-2010, n.d.; 207473 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Meeting Agendas, 2006-2011; 207474 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - "Small Times" magazine articles, 2001-2006; 207475 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Series III: Nanotechnology Initiatives, 2002-2015; 207479
  - Planning, Funding, and Evaluating Nanotechnology Research Centers and Initiatives, 2007; 207476 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - National Nanotechnology Initiative, 2003-2004; 207477 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - National Nanotechnology Initiative, 2005-2008; 207478 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Chemical Industry R & D Roadmap for Nanomaterials, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Advanced Energy Consortium (AEC) Planning, 2005-2010 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Advanced Energy Consortium (AEC) Agreement, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Advanced Energy Consortium (AEC) Nanoscience & Nanotechnology Materials Survey, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Armchair Quantum Wire (AQW) Appropriations Request, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Armchair Quantum Wire (AQW) project planning, 2008-2009 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Armchair Quantum Wire (AQW) change requests, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Armchair Quantum Wire (AQW) project, 2009-2010 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Armchair Quantum Wire (AQW) year 1 review, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - CENTAN: HARC (Houston Advanced Research Center) Proposal, 2007-2008; 207481 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - CONTACT files - DVD's, 2005-2007; 207502 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - CONTACT (1 of 2 - Alice Chow), 2008-2013 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - CONTACT Proposal 2007 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - CENTAN Proposal HARC 2007 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - "Nanotechnology" The BOC Group (Dr Smalley Interviewed) 2005, 2001-2005 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - CONTACT Commerce outreach correspondence, 2006-2007; 207501 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - CONTACT Long-term funding strategy, 2007; 207500 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - CONTACT Program grant/cooperative agreement, 2007-2009; 207498 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - CONTACT: TAMUSIC (Texas & Missouri Universities Scietific Interdisciplinary Collaborators), 2007-2010; 207499 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - CONTACT (Consortium for Nanomaterials for Aerospace Commerce and Technology) Program activity, 2008; 207484 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - CONTACT Program activity, 2009; 207485 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - CONTACT Program activity, 2010; 207486 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - CONTACT program Interim Performance Report, April 2008; 207542 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - CONTACT program Annual Performance Report: Period: October 4, 2007 to October 3, 2008, November 2008; 207541 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - CONTACT program Interim Performance Report: Period: October 4, 2008 to April 3, 2009, April 2009; 207540 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - CONTACT program Annual Performance Report: Period: October 4, 2008 to October 3, 2009, November 2009; 207539 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - CONTACT program Interim Performance Report: Period: October 4, 2009 to April 3, 2010, April 2010; 207538 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - CONTACT program Annual Performance Report: Period: October 6, 2009 to October 5, 2010, November 2010; 207537 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - CONTACT program Interim Performance Report: Period: October 6, 2010 to April 5, 2011, April 2011; 207536 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - CONTACT program Annual Performance Report: Period: October 6, 2010 to October 5, 2011, November 2011; 207535 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - CONTACT program Interim Performance Report: Period: October 6, 2011 to April 5, 2012, April 2012; 207509 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - CONTACT program Final Performance Report: Period: October 4, 2007 to February 5, 2013, February 2013; 207508 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - CONTACT program annual review meeting, August 19, 2008; 207546; 7 Sony Handycam miniDVD's (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - CONTACT program annual review meeting, September 29-October 1, 2009; 207547 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - CONTACT program annual review meeting, October 13-14, 2010; 207548 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - CONTACT program 4th Annual Technical and Annual Review, November 8-10, 2011; 207545 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - CONTACT program Executive Committee meeting, March 26, 2010; 207504 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - CONTACT program follow-up meeting, March 22, 2012; 207503 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Jupiter Icy Moons Orbiter (JIMO) (1 of 3), 2004 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Jupiter Icy Moons Orbiter (JIMO) (2 of 3), 2004 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Jupiter Icy Moons Orbiter (JIMO) (3 of 3), 2004 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Lancer (Lockheed-Martin) Pilot, 2005-2008 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Lancer (Lockheed-Martin) Research & Development, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Lancer (Lockheed-Martin) articles, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Lancer (Lockheed-Martin) conference DVD, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Lancer (Lockheed-Martin) collaboration site, 2008-2010 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Lancer (Lockheed-Martin) Overviews, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Lancer (Lockheed-Martin) C-Lance Proposal, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 17)